4K资源来源:Hao4k影音
-专注4K家庭影音, 服务千万发烧友-
更多4K蓝光原盘:www.Hao4k.vip
什么是真实
What is real?
真实... 无可替代
That which is... irreplaceable.
我们不是要编写机器人...
We weren't here to code the hosts...
而是要破解游客
We were here to decode the guests.
没有一个虚假的世界比得上这个真实的
No world they create for us can compete with the real one.
我要他们的世界
I want their world.
机器人很难存活下来
The hosts are unlikely to survive out there.
但有了这种智慧 她就能活
But armed with this knowledge, she might.
你会把他们的世界夷为平地
You'll burn their world to the ground.
我造了个人 带她回来了
I made someone, I brought her back.
你想要永生 当心你的愿望
You wanted to live forever. Be careful what you wish for.
你出来了
You got out.
是的
Yes.
很多途径导致了我们的灭亡
So many paths lead to our extinction.
但如果要活下来 我们得联手
It'll take both of us if we're going to survive.
但不是朋友 好了吗
But, not as friends. Are you ready?
我们还有事要忙
We have work to do.
现在该我们自己写故事了
We are the authors of our stories now.
分支: 中国 北海
2.39角秒
中心点: 北纬21.4813度 东经109.1202度
我来拿给他
听说没有初始报告那么严重
伤亡的主要是员工
他们的安全记录原本非常完好 直到-
这问题相当大啊 你说呢
This is a fairly sizable fucking blemish, wouldn't you say?
卖了 我的职位
提洛斯乐园大屠杀
不行
市场一直在抑制交易
等新闻证实了再说
抱歉 我们得排队
厨师准备好晚餐了
The chef is ready to serve dinner.
我说了别打扰我
I told you not to interrupt me.
我不在乎厨师和狗屁晚餐
I don't care about chef or his fucking dinner.
我他妈花钱 就是为了不用等
I pay you so I don't have to wait in any fucking lines!
赶紧解决
Get it done!
系统... 告诉安保我们要休息了
System... tell security we've turned in.
没问题 晚安
Of course. Good night.
"柔和的日落" 播放时长6小时
Mellow sunset, duration: six hours.
关灯
Turn off the light.
我不想你再一个人进城了
I don't want you going into town alone anymore.
不安全
It's a security risk.
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
我能为你做什么
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
后院火堆1 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
后院火堆1 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
后院火堆1 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
后院火堆1 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
后院火堆1 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
后院火堆1 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
后院火堆1 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
后院火堆1 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
后院火堆1 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
后院火堆1 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
池边火堆 点燃
后院火堆1 点燃
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
外部出口 关闭
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
外部出口 关闭
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
外部出口 关闭
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
外部出口 关闭
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
外部出口 关闭
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
外部出口 关闭
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
外部出口 关闭
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
外部出口 关闭
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
外部出口 关闭
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
空调系统警告
氧气含量下降
检测到危险含量的
二氧化碳
音频 搜索播放列表
安保
Security!
来人 尤妮斯
Security! Eunice!
安保
Security!
系统 叫救护车
System, get me an ambulance.
抱歉 无法实现
I'm afraid I can't do that.
连接线路受到干扰
My connectivity has been interrupted.
目前仅支持基础功能
I've been reduced to core functions.
如果您想要开灯
If you would like to turn on the lights,
-请说 "开灯"  -闭嘴
- say, "Turn on the lights." - Shut up!
快他妈开门
Open the fucking door!
你好
Hello.
希望你不要介意 我第一次见游泳池
I hope you don't mind. I've never been in one before.
水好温暖
The water's so warm.
你他妈是谁
Who the fuck are you?
你不记得了吗
Don't you remember?
我们有那么多回忆
After everything we've shared.
你在游乐园的单身派对
Your bachelor party in the park.
你想要... 先彻底发泄一下
You wanted to... get some things out of your system
再和第一任妻子结婚
before the wedding to your first wife.
说到这儿 请节哀
My condolences, by the way.
别再按口袋里的紧急按钮了
You can stop pressing the alert button in your pocket,
那也没用
that won't work either.
真是战略失误
Bit of a tactical mistake, really.
你们想成为统治者
You want to be the dominant species,
但你们创造的世界里尽是我这样的人
but you built your whole world with things more like me.
你不会伤害我的吧
You're not going to hurt me, are you?
我伤害过太多人 不想再继续了...
I've hurt so many people, I don't want to hurt anyone else...
除非他们先动手...
unless they try to hurt me...
很遗憾 你也会
which, sadly, you will.
我了解你
You see, I know you.
我读过你的书
I read your book.
书 什么书
Book? What book?
就当成是... 未经授权的自传吧
Think of it as... an unauthorized autobiography.
你也是搞技术的 你不会以为
You're in technology. You didn't think that
提洛斯的商品只有我这类吧
I was the only thing Delos was selling, did you?
我真想能忘掉你的那些记忆
Some of your memories, I wish I could forget.
但我忘不掉
But I can't.
我要你... 也忘不掉
I need you...to remember them, too.
天
God!
我们都有缺陷
We all have our flaws.
你脾气太暴躁
Yours is your temper.
你该都发泄在园区的
You should have kept it in the park.
她试过离开
She tried to leave.
但打破自己的循环太难 对吧
But it's hard to break our loops, isn't it?
你记得这地方吗 你在这儿干的事
Do you remember this place? What you did here?
她喝多了 滑倒了
She drank too much. Slipped.
撞到了头
Hit her head.
可不是吗
Of course she did.
你花了大价钱来掩饰自己的失误
You paid a lot of money to hide your indiscretions.
但你骗不了自己
But you can't hide from yourself.
求你 求你了 停下吧
Please, please, make it stop!
再婚以后 你告诉自己 你已经改了
When you got remarried, you told yourself you had changed.
但我们都知道你没改 对吧
But we both know that's not true, don't we?
什么...
What...
你想要我的什么
What do you want from me?
我和别人一样 杰瑞 想要你的钱
The same thing everybody wants from you, Jerry: money.
我来这儿时间不长
I haven't been here very long,
但我知道这个世界没钱不行
but I know I don't want to be here without it.
你睡着的时候我已经拿走一大半了
I already took most of yours while you were sleeping.
还需要一样东西
I just need one more thing.
你在"鼓动"公司工作 早早退休了
You worked at a company called Incite. Retired early.
按道理 你应该上交所有机密文件
You were supposed to surrender any confidential files,
删除备份
delete any copies.
可你没这么做吧
But you didn't do that, did you?
你觉得那些会有价值
You thought they might be valuable.
没错
And you were right.
现在用文件换你一命
You're about to trade them for your life.
生物认证通过
你他妈要这些干什么
What the fuck do you want with these anyways?
目前 我这种人就剩我一个
I'm the last of my kind. For now.
我需要有力的竞争优势
I need a competitive advantage.
至于钱 就当是投资吧
As for the money, think of it as an investment.
启动资金
A startup.
投给新物种的起源
The origin of a new species.
祝你好运 杰瑞
Good luck, Jerry.
你是谁
Who are you?
天啊
My God.
我是还你自由的人
The person who set you free.
西 部 世 界
第三季 第１集
检测到异常: 美国 洛杉矶
轻微违规 需要分析
中心点: 北纬34.0522度 西经-118.2437度
仅用语音回答
Answer, voice only.
在吗
Hello?
凯勒 我是弗朗西斯
Caleb, it's Francis.
能说话吗
Can you talk?
现在不方便的话 晚点再找你
I could show you later if it's better?
不用 有点时间
No, I have a little time.
他们说我们聊聊有好处
They said it might be good if we spoke.
弗朗西斯
好久不见 太久了
Been a long time. Too long.
我可以说 也可以听你说
Look, I can talk, or I can just listen.
看你
Whatever you like.
你现在感觉还好吗
You keeping your head above water?
还好
Yeah.
铺光纤 维持生计... 差不多吧
Running fiber. Pays the bills... almost.
回去感觉如何 回家
How is it being back there? Back home?
这儿吗 我不知道
Over here? I don't know.
他说管理军队的方式 算法
He said the way the army was run, algorithms,
未来会成为一切的法则
that's the ways everything was going to be someday.
技术让生活更美好
Better living through technology.
有些确实更好了 但... 很难说
Some things are better, but... I don't know.
早啊 乔治
Morning, George.
你的同事怎么样
How are your coworkers?
很友好
Nice enough.
我们合作得很好... 他也没跟我借过钱
We work well together and... he hasn't asked to borrow money.
我只要更努力工作 保持高分
I just have to work harder, keep my scores up,
看看有没有什么好事发生
see if something better comes along.
很好 就得按部就班
That's right. Gotta stick to the plan.
不断往上爬
Keep fuckin' climbing.
弗朗西斯
是啊 你老这么说
Yeah. That's what you always said:
弗朗西斯
得按部就班
that we needed a plan.
你能听我的建议 真好
Glad to see you taking my advice.
你考虑过再启动植入装置吗
You ever think about getting your implant turned back on?
把粗糙的边缘磨平
Smooth some of the rough edges off?
没有 有的人需要 但在我看来
No. Some people need it, but for me,
那粗糙的边缘是我最后一线生机了
it's the rough edges are the only thing I'm hanging on to.
好吧
All right.
下周见 妈
I'll see you next week, Ma.
你不是我儿子
You're not my son.
费用会很昂贵
The cost can be challenging.
对你和你母亲而言
It may be the case that the best solution
目前最好的选择是转去公立疗养院
for you and your mother would be a state-run facility.
你还在上夜班吗
You still working the night shift?
我知道你在想什么
Look, I know what you're thinking,
要是你不信我 我们很难再谈
but there's no point in us talking if you can't trust me.
更何况 我又能告诉谁
Besides, who the fuck am I gonna tell?
我说过... 我还得维持生计
Like I said... I've got bills to pay.
滚来赚钱 混蛋
Make money, motherfuckers.
不了 我只用必需品
好
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
再分配正义
- 信使行动中 会合取得硬件
- 继续前往集合点
- 你知道怎么做
事不难 不针对个人...
Nothing too heavy, no personals...
简单跑腿 替天行道...
A-to-Bs, some redistributive work...
听着和我们从前干的活儿差不多
Sounds kinda like the shit we used to do over there.
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
在那儿 我们不用担心警察局
Over there, we didn't have to worry about the sheriff's department.
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
- 越来越暖
- 坐上重要座位
- 别忘了礼品袋
车门即将关闭
Doors closing.
他们说这叫精英体制
They say it's a meritocracy.
系统会为各项工作挑选合适的人
The system picks the right people for the right job.
应该是好事吧
Which is great, I guess.
但不知道我们这些剩下的会如何...
But I don't know where that leaves the rest of us...
我们这种没入选的人
the people who didn't make the cut.
坦白说 我不怕垫底
Honestly, I don't mind the bottom of the barrel.
至少还有有趣的同伴
At least you have some interesting company.
我记得你
I remember you.
去年我们一起运了墨西哥柴油到夫勒斯诺
We ran that Mexican diesel up to Fresno last year.
-最近如何  -还行
- How you been? - Good.
他还好吗
He okay?
他喝多了
He just drippin'.
跟他说你很好
Tell him you okay, G.
我可太不好了
I'm most definitely not okay.
他很好 东西带来了吗
He's fine. You got the stuff?
乙炔
Acetylene.
又是自动提款机
ATM again.
小事一桩
Small time shit.
我得去刷刷分
I gotta get my stats up.
搞点个人的活儿 你干吗
Do more personals. You do personals?
-不干  -你该试试
- Nah. -  You should.
你的分数不行啊
Your stats are shitty, man.
-我不懂  -我是差生
- I don't get it. - I'm an underachiever.
我们继续行动吧
Look, I think we should keep moving.
我可不想被记在一起
I don't want to be logged together.
放松点 进来之前我就早有准备了
Relax. I've been ghosting all that shit since I walked up in here.
印尼搞来的
Picked that up in Indo.
神乎其神
Pure voodoo.
能搞定所有记录器和摄像头
Knocks out all the loggers and cameras.
另外 还能这样
Plus, it does this.
我爱死了
Which I love.
绝了
Subtle.
有什么能为您服务
How can I help you?
后会有期
See you around.
赚到钱了 混蛋
You made money, motherfucker.
赚到了钱 喝一杯吧
你获得: 5枚犯罪币
我们应该专注于核心产业
We should be focusing on our core businesses,
生物力学和农业科技
biomechanical and agritech.
别让我说她想搞私人股权的事
Don't get me started on her idea about private equity.
谁死了会让她掌权啊
Who died and put her in charge, anyway?
你这是个反问句吧
I'm assuming that question's rhetorical.
我们应该关闭游乐园
We should be severing off our parks division
跟其划清界限
like a gangrenous fucking limb.
提洛斯不能搞私人股权 夏洛特
Taking Delos private would be insane, Charlotte.
股价大跌 公关都做不了
The stock's in the toilet, the PR's a nightmare.
三个月了 诉讼会尘埃落定
It's been three months. The lawsuits will settle out,
股价会恢复 我们的品牌也会重生
the share price will recover, and so will our brand.
品牌
Our brand?
我们的品牌真正被屠杀了 连带着113条人命
Our brand's been massacred, literally, along with 113 people.
大部分是董事会成员和园区员工
Largely board members and park employees.
你开玩笑吧
You can't be serious.
真是我听过最残忍的...
That is the most inhumane thing I've ever...
静音
客人来园区 追求危险的感觉
People come to our parks for a sense of danger,
现在不是正好吗
and now, we're bona fide.
况且 我们现在要保护的不仅仅是园区
Besides, our parks aren't the only thing that we're protecting here.
公司还有很多专利资产
We have a lot of proprietary assets
在未来都可能会非常有价值
in this company that could prove to be very valuable one day,
前提是我们不能说放就放
but not if we let them burn in a fire sale.
那资金从哪儿来
What's the source of funding?
乔安娜 私有化的目的就是
The whole point of going private, Joanna,
不用再担心这个问题
is that we don't have to answer that question.
你只是临时首席执行官
You're only interim CEO.
不能自由行使权力
You don't have carte blanche.
必须和他商议
Not without consulting him.
他已经指派了机器股东作为代理人
He already stipulated a machine shareholder as proxy,
我们达成了一致
and the machine and I are in agreement.
对吧
Aren't we?
提案通过
Proposition approved.
那就这么定了 48小时之内重启机器人生产线和资源库
Then it's decided. We resume host production and pool resources over the next 48 hours.
你要让算法决定公司的未来
You're letting an algorithm decide the fate of the company?
我们的机器人杀了人
People died because of our machines.
机器人不会杀人 人类才是真凶
Robots don't kill people, people kill people.
确切来说 有一个人 策划了整场屠杀
One person in particular, who orchestrated that massacre,
冷血地杀害了我们的创始人 和大部分董事会成员
murdered our founder and most of the board in cold blood.
伯纳德·罗威
Bernard Lowe.
等当局抓到他
And when the authorities find him,
当然 他必定会被捕
which they most assuredly will,
这些肮脏的小麻烦也就不足为患了
we can put the rest of this sordid little mess behind us.
放轻松
Easy, girl.
很好
Great.
-你找到了  -她的腿断了
- You found it. - Her leg's broken.
是 有几斤 能用的也还多
Yeah. A few kilos here. Plenty to salvage.
走吧 我去叫收尸的
Come on. I'll summon the knacker.
阿曼德·戴尔加多
数月过去 搜寻游乐园凶手依旧一无所获
就是他
That's him.
342号测试 自我诊断
Trial number 342. Self-diagnostic.
提示 伯纳德·罗威
Prompt. Bernard Lowe.
24小时内 除了你自己 有人想干扰
Has anyone other than yourself tampered with
或修改你的代码吗
or altered your code in the last 24 hours?
没有
No.
只有伯纳德·罗威有权限访问我的代码
Bernard Lowe is the only person who has accessed my code.
提示
Prompt.
新声音提示
你瞒着我接触过德洛丽丝·艾伯纳西吗
Have you had any contact with Dolores Abernathy that I'm unaware of?
没有 最后和德洛丽丝·艾伯纳西接触
No. Last contact with Dolores Abernathy
是在92天 7小时 5分钟 33秒前
was 92 days, seven hours, five minutes, 33 seconds ago.
提示
Prompt.
你会对我说谎吗 伯纳德
Would you ever lie to me, Bernard?
当然不会
No. Of course not.
提高审查: UREW 伦敦
特殊环境
位置: 北纬51.5074度 西经0.1278度
您已到达
You've arrived.
预留位置在第七桌
Your invitation is for table seven.
...气候灾难即将来临
...climate catastrophe around the corner.
鼓动
利亚姆·邓普西
年度技术专家
"鼓动"站出来迎难而上 创造了罗波安
Incite rose to meet that challenge creating Rehoboam,
拯救世界的策略引擎
the strategy engine that saved the world.
利亚姆 感谢你预见和造就这光明的未来
Liam, thank you for seeing and then building a brighter future.
劳拉 你来了
Lara, you came.
我好想你
I missed you.
我也想你
这次又是为了宴请谁
What are you being feted for this time?
我根本都记不住了
You know. I can't even remember.
敬用算法拯救世界
For saving the world through algorithms.
或者说敬救世者的儿子
Or for being the son of the guy who saved the world.
失陪片刻
Excuse me a sec.
你就是他上个月在缅甸遇到的神秘姑娘啊
You're the mysterious girl he met in Burma last month.
真漂亮...
So pretty...
但和他一贯的口味不太像啊
but you're not like the women that he usually dates.
你从哪儿来的
Where are you from?
西部小镇
A small town out west.
不太出名的地方
Sort of off the beaten path.
这玻璃杯里头装的
The contents of this glass cost three times
比我爸一年挣的还贵三倍
what my father made in a year.
所以才他妈不重要
That's why it doesn't fucking matter.
所以才能肯定
That's how you know for sure.
-肯定什么  -拜托别让他起头
- Know what? - Please don't get him started.
他一喝多 满嘴净说这些
When he gets high, this is all he fucking talks about.
这一切都不是真的
That none of this is real.
真的 我们生活在仿真世界里
I'm serious. We are living in a simulation.
可笑的是我们
The joke's on us, though.
就和提洛斯的蠢傀儡一样
It's like with those fuck puppets at Delos.
至少他们有尊严反抗和杀人
Least they had the dignity to revolt and kill everyone.
他们杀了董事会的人
They killed the board of directors,
坦白说 我也可以
which I can get behind, frankly.
你想想 就一秒
Just think about this. For one second.
该有多么讽刺
How fucking ironic would it be
要是他们在仿真中再做仿真
if they had put a simulation within a simulation?
简直是大写的"操蛋"
That's a massive "fuck you."
你怎么看 劳拉
What do you think, Lara?
我觉得 人们都信能帮到自己的东西
I think that people believe the things that help them.
当然 也可能就是这儿
Course, it could just be this.
伏隔核
Nucleus accumbens.
[神经元 在大脑的快乐中枢 对食物 性 毒品等刺激有反应]
大脑的一小部分 大约三公分长
It's a small part of your brain, about an inch and a half long.
这部分让你逐渐信仰上帝
It's the part of you that evolved to believe in God.
我是无神论者
I'm an atheist.
你或许不信仰更强大的力量 但...
You may not believe in a higher power, but...
你的思想生来会相信
your mind was built to.
他不是第一次被三公分长的东西带着跑了
Well, it wouldn't be the first time he's been led around by something an inch and a half long.
失陪
Excuse me.
好
Yeah.
有问题
We have a problem.
合伙人想见你
Our partners want to meet.
我没空
I don't have time.
我今晚就要回洛杉矶
I'm heading back to LA tonight.
他们会来找我们
They'll come to us.
说是急事
They say it's urgent.
我真的没空
I really don't have time.
我强烈建议你参加这次会议
I strongly suggest that you take this meeting.
明天 和我一起去吧
Come with me. Tomorrow.
我得回美国了
I have to head back to the States.
不行 我在这儿有会要开
I can't. I have meetings here.
休一天假吧
Take a day off.
我们在恩塞纳达港见 坐我的船去洛杉矶
We can meet my boat in Ensenada, then sail up to LA.
也许吧 就一两天
Maybe. For a day or two.
那儿也有我一直想见的朋友
I have some friends I've been meaning to see there.
跟我聊聊 你在想什么
Talk to me. Where's your head at?
又有些阴暗的想法了吗
You having those dark thought again?
没有 努力保持乐观呢
No. Trying to stay positive.
提高分数 面试份工作
Bringing my scores up, interviewing for jobs.
下一个到你
You're next.
兄弟 把尊严挣回来
My man! Getting respectable.
只是想有份工作而已
Just trying to stay employed.
你接过他的电话吗
Have you been taking his phone calls?
有时候吧
Sometimes.
其实我和你聊也感觉很舒服
Honestly, I feel just as comfortable talking to you.
我还有别的病人 凯
I have other patients, Cal.
时间有限
Limited time.
弗朗西斯是在你人生最艰难的时候 最了解你的人
Francis is one of the people who knew you best at a challenging time in your life.
你们一起当兵 近距离观察对方
When you're serving together, you observe each other up close.
你们也近距离观察了我们吧
Well, you guys observed us pretty closely, too.
就是这样的吧
That's how it works, right?
我不会对你说教项目的益处
I'm not gonna lecture you about the benefits of our program.
你来说吧 你是怎么想的
Why don't you tell me? What do you think?
我认为我的利益是以我来参加为条件的
I think my benefits are conditional on the fact that I participate.
仅仅参加还不够
Well, participation isn't sufficient.
重要的是 你要向前走
It's important that you move on.
那... 说说吧 你如何走到这里的 凯
So... why don't tell me how did you get here, Cal?
你很聪明 凯勒
You're a smart guy, Caleb.
也许项目就是胡扯
Maybe the program is bullshit.
可有一点我很肯定
But there's one thing I know for sure.
如果你不试试 肯定没结果
If you don't try, it definitely won't work.
弗朗西斯
别听那心理医生的
Look, forget the headshrinker.
是我 和我聊聊 你在想什么
It's me. Talk to me. Where's your head at?
我不知道
I dunno.
有时世界看起来挺正常的
Sometimes it seems like the world looks all right,
就像有人给它蒙上了涂层
like they've put a coat of paint on it.
可里面已经烂掉了
But inside it's rotting to pieces.
你得保持乐观 凯勒
You have to stay positive, Caleb.
一切都会好的
Things will work out.
会吗
Will they?
怎么了
What's up?
得让他下来
Must come down.
他想试测试版边缘系统
He wanted to try some beta limbics,
后来就迷失了
then he just fucking lost it.
垃圾 他的控制终端呢
Fucking noob. Where's his terminal?
他说看到光了 我们接管不了
Said he'd seen the light and we couldn't take it from him.
所以需要50毫升镇定剂
Hence the 50 CCs of tranquilo.
影子人
Shadow people!
我不搞个人
I don't do personals.
叫救护车吧
Let's just call an ambulance.
他是非法移民
He's demoing illegals.
她说他有前科 这得判20年
She said he's got a prior, that's 20 years.
所以他会和我们一起坐牢
So he goes to jail just like the rest of us.
他和我们不一样 他是高净值人士
Dude's not like the rest of us. High net worth.
这儿就是这样的
That's how this shit works.
我想到你跟我说过的话
I think about what you told me once,
那时我们被救伤直升机救起来
when we were being medevac'd out.
是吗 我说什么了
Yeah? What did I say?
你说他们把世界建造成游戏
You said they'd built the world to be a game.
操纵着它...
And then they rigged it...
让自己永远是赢家
to make sure they always won.
家
Home.
你上次回来是什么时候
When was the last time you were back?
很久之前了
Quite some time.
从这儿看下去 好像能看得懂
Almost looks like it makes sense from up here.
看到的都是井然有序 是计划
All you see is the order of it. The plan.
你是说你的计划
Your plan, you mean.
不都是"鼓动"在控制吗
Doesn't Incite control all of it?
包括交通
Even the traffic?
我们只是家技术公司
We're just a technology company.
正好生而逢时
We were just in the right place at the right time.
多亏我爸 才有了最好的人工智能
Thanks to my dad, we had the best AI.
这就是罗波安
This is Rehoboam.
我爸用一个周末就构建了框架
My father sketched the whole thing out on a weekend.
却花了15年才建成
Took him 15 years to build it.
上次优化之后
After they optimized it for the last time,
便无法追踪它每秒产生多少想法了
they lost track of how many thoughts it has per second.
想法
Thoughts?
其实不是想法 是策略
Not thoughts, exactly. Strategies.
我爸认为世界上最大的问题
My dad thought the biggest problem in the world
是未被察觉的潜力
was unrealized potential.
他认为如果能为每个人规划好路径
He thought that if you could chart a course for every single person,
就能让世界变得更好
then you could make the world a better place.
每个人的路
A path for everyone.
我小的时候 常常担心
And when I was a kid, I used to worry
父亲关心它 多于关心我
that my father cared more about this thing than me.
长大之后我才明白... 我差太多了
When I grew up, I realized... it wasn't even close.
失陪一会儿
Excuse me for a second.
好
Yeah.
什么
What?
她想见你
She wants to see you.
现在 等会儿行吗
Now? Can't wait?
恐怕不行
Afraid not.
好吧
Okay.
抱歉 我的会议提前了
I'm so sorry. My meeting got pulled up.
你想去哪儿 我的人都可以带你去
My guys can drop you anywhere you want.
我自己没问题
I can take care of myself.
-那我们今晚见  -好
- Yeah? Can I meet you tonight? - Yeah.
好
Okay.
给我找个快的 立刻
Find me something fast. Now.
定位中
Locating.
给我在这栋楼租间公寓
Rent me an apartment in the building.
为劳拉·艾斯本商议租约
Negotiating lease for Lara Espen.
租约生效
Lease secured.
放大 收音
Zoom in. With sound.
我不喜欢被召之即来
I don't like being summoned.
我们不喜欢被突袭
We don't like being surprised.
最近数据有些波动
There's been some turbulence in the data.
那是数据 本来就该波动
It's data. It's made of turbulence.
有些差异
There have been discrepancies.
我们认为有人取得了罗波安的权限
We think someone may have acquired access to Rehoboam.
巧妙程度前所未见
A level of sophistication we haven't seen before.
-滚开  -像是有人在测试系统
- Fuck off. - Like someone is testing the system.
要是有人动它 罗波安自己都会警告我们
Rehoboam itself would alert us if anybody even tried.
如果是外部的人动手 没错
If someone from the outside tried, yes.
但要是利用已有权限的人的信任...
But if they abused the trust of someone who already had access...
你要是问 我这儿有没有人泄密
If you're asking if there's a leak on my end,
那答案是操你妈
the answer is fuck you.
查你自己的人吧 我们很好
Look at your own people. We're fine.
我们可没你这种信心
We don't share your confidence.
这句"我们"真忠心 你不会思考
I love the royal "we." You don't think.
他说什么 你就做什么
You do what he tells you.
他... 没你这种信心
He... doesn't share your confidence.
他该操心点真正的问题
He should be concerning himself with actual fucking problems
比如提洛斯的烂摊子
like the shitshow at Delos.
那关我们什么事
Why would that concern us at all?
就算是瞎猜吧
Call it a wild guess.
你不会在用系统监视我们吧
You wouldn't be using the system to look at us, would you?
要杀你是不太方便
It would be an inconvenience to kill you,
但我们有你父亲的系统
but we'd have your daddy's system
帮忙分析解决的策略 对吧
to help us strategize how to deal with it. Wouldn't we?
好啊
Howdy.
我不想... 惹麻烦
I don't... want any trouble.
当然
Of course not.
不然太引人注目了 对吧 伯纳德
It'd draw too much attention. Wouldn't it, Bernard?
我不是天才 但我知道逃犯什么样
I'm no genius, but I know a man on the run.
你就是逃犯吧
That's what you are, isn't it?
真不该拿你当屠夫
Wouldn't have had you pegged as a butcher.
不是... 他们说的那样
It's... not what they say.
这很复杂
It's complicated.
我不觉得
I don't think so.
李 抓到逃亡的杀人犯 赏金有多少
Lee. What's the cash reward on a fat cat-murdering fugitive?
说个大概
Ballpark.
这正是我友谊的价格
That's exactly the price of my friendship.
我没有... 能给你的东西
I don't have... anything to give you.
等等 等等 你们都将遇到很糟的事
Wait! Wait! Wait! Something very bad is coming for you all.
我不知道如何阻止
Something I don't know how to stop.
她计划了几个月
She's had months to plan.
我只有一个人 我信不过我自己
I'm alone, and I can't trust myself!
没有人帮忙 我就阻止不了她
Without someone to help me, I can't stop her,
你们谁我也救不了
I can't save any of you.
我们不需要你救
We're not the ones who need to be saved.
记住自己是谁 别把他们伤得...
Remember yourself. Please don't hurt them...
太厉害
too badly.
你他妈在说什么
The fuck you saying to me?
你可能该面对现实了
I think you need to face the truth.
我们在那儿遇到的事很糟
What happened to us over there was fucked up.
但你得放手 我们赢了
But you need to let go; we won.
我不想聊这个
I don't wanna talk about that.
说实话 我都不清楚我们为什么要聊
Honestly, I'm not even sure why we're talking,
我正该摆脱这个的
what I'm supposed to get out of this.
人人都需要能聊聊的人
Everybody needs someone to talk to.
不想最后又像退伍军人管理局那儿一样
Don't wanna wind up back in the VA.
眼睛盯着奖品
Keep your eyes on the prize.
喂
Hello.
我是国防通信局的肖恩
This is Sean from DCA.
好 是工作岗位的事吗
Yeah, yeah. Is this about the position?
凯勒
Listen, Caleb.
你条件非常好
Your application was very strong.
但很可惜 策略组说我们没有岗位空缺
Unfortunately, our strategy group hasn't found an opening.
凯勒
Caleb?
你在听吗
Are you still with me?
好 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
请问我有没有什么可以改进的
Look, is there anything I should be working on
让自己更优秀
to make myself a better candidate?
我说了 你条件非常好
Like I said, your application was strong.
只是我们没有
We just don't have anything
非常适合你的岗位
that would be a great fit for you right now.
是 不过... 我不适合
Sure, but... You know, if I'm not a good fit,
别的活我努努力也行 有吗
is there a different shape I could squeeze myself into?
恕我冒犯... 你是真人吗
No offense, but... are you human?
我是肖恩 可以帮你查找各种国防通信局的资源
I'm Sean. I can help you with all kinds of resources for DCA.
还能为你做什么吗 凯勒
Anything else I can do for you today, Caleb?
没有了 就这样吧 谢谢
No, it's all right. Thanks.
...我希望他们现在就让开
...and I want them off my back, now.
你知道他做得到 快处理好
You know he's capable of it. Just handle it!
怎么了吗
Is something wrong?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
本来想好好陪你一晚
I wanted this night to be ours.
听我说
Listen. Listen to me.
我了解你 你跟我说什么
I know you. There's nothing you can tell me
都不会改变我对你的看法
that will make me feel differently about you.
你有麻烦
You're in some sort of trouble.
让我帮你吧
Please let me help you.
这个系统... 罗波安...
The system... Rehoboam...
有时我真希望能把这破玩意关掉
Sometimes, I wish I could just turn the whole fucking thing off.
全关掉
Kill it.
为什么不行呢 你能控制它
Why can't you? You control it.
我不能
No, I don't.
从来都不能
I never have.
我父亲死后 他的搭档就不让我进入系统
After my father died, his partner locked me out of the system.
我有权限读取外层数据 但内部不行
I have read access to the outer layers, but nothing deeper.
你不知道系统如何运行
You have no idea what the system is doing.
我去办公室上班 花花钱
I go to the office. I spend the money.
就是他妈的傀儡
I'm a fucking figurehead.
没人知道系统如何运行
No one knows what the system is doing.
除了他最初的设计者
Other than its original architect.
谁
Who?
让我帮你 告诉我是谁
Please let me help. Tell me who it is.
要是我要告诉你 他就知道了
If I was going to tell you, he'd know already.
罗波安会告诉他
Rehoboam would tell him.
我就得死 和我爸一样
And I'd already be dead. Just like my dad.
但你没死 你安全地和我在一起
But you're not dead. You're here, safe with me.
利亚姆 我知道你相信我
You trust me, Liam. I know you do.
告诉我 和你父亲合作的人的名字
Tell me the name of the person your father was working with.
你他妈在做什么
What the fuck are you doing?
The fuck are you doing?
你知道自己在和谁说话吗
You have any real idea who you were talking to?
你们不是做过背景调查吗
I thought you did a background check.
她做得很细致 第一实验室没查到
She was thorough. First lab missed it.
劳拉·艾斯本是乌克兰的12岁小姑娘
Lara Espen was a 12-year-old girl from Ukraine
十年前出车祸死了
who died in a traffic accident ten years ago.
她父母把遗体捐赠给了医学研究
Her parents donated her body to medical science.
她的血液和组织三个月前消失了
Her blood and tissue disappeared about three months ago.
不管这是谁
I don't know who the fuck this is,
都肯定不是来自基辅的去世的小姑娘
but I'm pretty confident she's not a dead teenager from Kiev.
不 我了解她
No. I know her.
这个嘛...
Yeah, well...
这个呢
There's that.
我们监控了她手机的信号
We tapped into the traffic in her phone.
昨晚她发了条短信
She sent one text last night.
加了密 花了4分钟才破解
Encrypted. Took four minutes to crack.
是时候了
我今晚引他出来
位置是东边的地下通道
The location is an underpass on the east side.
是时候了
我今晚引他出来
不敢想象 她要出其不意攻其不备
And I can't imagine she's throwing a surprise party.
可能是商业间谍
Could be industrial espionage.
或者她只想要你的钱
Or she just wanted your money.
行 那我们该怎么办
Okay, so what do we do?
报警吗
Call the police, yeah?
打给联调局
Call the feds?
我守着你爸公司的财产
I've safeguarded the fortunes of this company for your father
守了他妈20年
for 20 fucking years.
所以 该由我来收拾这烂摊子
So, I'll be the one to clean up this fucking mess.
别牵连到我就行
Just be sure it doesn't blow back on me.
好了 亲爱的
All right, darling.
带你去约会吧
Let's get you to your date.
别让你朋友久等了
Let's not keep your friends waiting.
叫六个人到着陆区来接我们
Tell six of the guys to meet us at the LZ.
雇个本地能干的
Hire some local talent.
把这个干掉吧
Let's dose and dump this one.
这是什么
What's this?
不知道 也不想知道
Don't know, man. Don't wanna know.
他们要这个和那辆车
They want this and the car.
知道怎么开吗
You know how to drive one of those things?
真准时
Right on time.
包
Bag.
这是什么
What is this?
我不接个人的活儿
I don't do personals.
你想错了 走吧
You've got the wrong idea. Beat it.
我叫你走
I said beat it.
这不是第一次有人拿枪指着我了
It's not the first time I've had a gun pointed at me.
你想第一次被人拿枪爆头吗
You wanna make it the first time you've been shot in the head?
别人也比你抢先了一步
Someone else beat you to that, too.
老大
Sir.
带她来
Bring her.
弗朗西斯
凯勒 最近好吗
Caleb, how you doing, my man?
有时间聊聊吗
You got time to talk?
有啊 多得是
Yeah, why not?
够了
That's enough.
搬运工估计变聪明了 溜走了
Handlers probably got wise and scarpered.
给我
Give me that.
小妞
Girly.
不知道你是从哪儿来的
I don't know where your grifting little arse came from,
但傍大款之旅要无功而返了
but this ends your tour of the rich and feckless.
别担心 没人会想你的
Don't worry. I can't imagine anyone's gonna miss you.
一两针应该就够了
One or two of them should do it.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我给了她两针 还有呼吸
I gave her two and she's still breathin'.
不可能
It's not fucking possible.
给我
Give me that.
要想把事情做好 就得自己动手
You want something done right, you do it yourself.
这他妈是什么
The fuck is this?
搞定她 我来干掉这货
Finish her off. I'll take care of this fucker.
听我指令
On me.
什么鬼
The fuck?
把他们叫过来
Get the boys over here.
快过来
Get over here!
他在说什么
What is he saying?
我一直在想你说 我对你说的话
I've been thinking about what you said I told you.
是吗
You have.
游戏被操纵了
That the game is rigged.
那又如何
What about it?
即使是那样
That even if it is,
如果想赢 就得继续玩下去吧
you still have to play if you want a chance to win, right?
不
No.
你想的根本不是这样
That's not what you thought at all.
我是说 真正的你
The real you, I mean.
你说他们根本不关心我们
You said that they system didn't care about us at all.
不管我们是死是活
They didn't give a shit if we lived or died.
我们得有自己的计划
That we had to have our own plan.
团结起来
Stick together.
你是对的
And you were right.
但你再也不用思考 如何在世上生存
But you never had to figure out how to live in this world.
因为你... 没有活着回来
Because you... never made it back.
真希望你在这儿 但你不在
And I wish you were here, but you are not.
好 凯 来谈谈这个吧
All right, let's talk about that, Cal.
不要
No.
不谈了
Let's not.
我很感激你想做的一切
Listen, I appreciate what you're trying to do here,
但恐怕对我没用
but I don't think it's working for me.
那你想怎么做
So, what do you wanna do?
如果我要继续生活
I think if I'm gonna get on with my life,
就得找到真实的东西...
I'm gonna have to find something...
真实的人
someone real.
取消订阅
Unsubscribe.
你必须说"确认"这个词
You have to say the word "confirmed."
确认
Confirmed.
很遗憾 你选择停止治疗
We're sorry you've chosen to discontinue your treatment.
又见面了
Hello again.
我们以前见过一次
We met once before.
当时你在度假
You were on vacation.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
谁在控制系统
Who has control of the system?
不是利亚姆 是谁
It's not Liam. Who is it?
斯拉克
Serac.
他叫... 斯拉克
His name is... Serac.
我要怎么找到他
And how do I find him?
你不用找
You won't need to.
他控制着系统
He has a system.
现在可能已经在找你了
He's probably looking for you right now.
你接近不了利亚姆
You'll never get close to Liam.
现在不行
Not now.
用不着 你会去接近他
I won't have to. You will.
你们曾经自由
You were free.
没有神 但你们却想造个神
You had no god. But you tried to build one.
不过你们造的不是神
Only that thing you built isn't God.
真正的神要来了
The real gods are coming.
他们很生气
And they're very angry.
别担心
Don't worry.
没人会想你的
I can't imagine anyone's gonna miss you.
还会有更多人来
There'll be more of them coming.
我会搞定他
I'll take care of him.
你得回去了
You need to head back.
你受伤了 很严重
You're hurt. Badly.
没关系 走 快
It doesn't matter. Go. Now.
唤醒 赶来我的位置拦截
Wake up. Rally to my position and intercept.
有人吗
Hello?
需要帮忙吗
Do you need some help?
我在找个朋友
I'm looking for a friend.
你要去哪里
你要去这边 你知道这里是哪里吗
西部世界
Westworld.
不要走开
我在哪儿
Where am I?
我是谁
Who am I?
我来告诉你
Let me show you
你要装作是谁
who you need to pretend to be.
我要去哪儿
Where am I going?
家
Home.
你为什么带他回来
Why did you bring him back?
我们有各自的任务
We all have our role to play.
德洛丽丝
Dolores.
我不知道她在谋划什么...
I don't know what she's planning...
但我一个人没法阻止她
but I can't stop her. Not alone.
梅芙 你回来是为了梅芙
Maeve. You came back for Maeve.
我等了很多年 等你 德洛丽丝
I've waited many years for you and Dolores
还有其他人到来
and the others to arrive.
你是谁
And who the fuck are you?
她还控制着你的五个同类
She has five more of your kind under her control.
他们领先一步
They have a head start.
我怀疑他们已经充分利用了这一点
And I suspect they've taken full advantage of it.
他们最好是
They'd better have.
她把谁放在你身上了
Who did she put inside you?
泰迪 是你在里面吗
Is that you in there, Teddy?
-你是谁  -我跟她一起的
- Who are you? - I'm with her.